[laughter]
I like to do that kind of things. I like
to do that kind of things. You guys know
me. You guys know me from the previous
videos. I'm all the time pranking one
way or another.
[music]
>> [music]
>> What's up, guys? Welcome back to the
channel.
We are again exploring some new
location. Me and my friend Karim.
>> Here he is. It's been already a while to
be honest since the last time that we
were exploring. So this time we are at
um the credential sterling. I'm going to
show you. So this is the building that
was used to be an insurance company uh
and been closed in 2022.
So this building here been um well been
closed in 2022 but been built in 1970.
So, look how it looks like. I was
looking to some videos um not long ago,
like actually a year ago, and all the
building was still intact, but
apparently
a lot of, you know, vandalism been
happening in this site, which is sad
that people keep destroying everything.
They they can't see actually the things
standing like in a really nice and
pleasant way. They like just to destroy
everything what is around. Right. It's
just it's just crazy. Huh?
>> Exactly. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Honestly,
>> look at that. They like all the glass.
>> This is just uh it's sad why people
actually do that. I just don't
understand. you know that kind of things
is needs to be preserved because this is
a huge building. This I believe that is
54 hectares uh uh which is massive
massive you will see a lot of um signs
saying uh dangerous building which is
completely normal because this is all
falling apart. I could hear like some
some noises inside but I believe that is
because it's um
>> windy. is windy and is
um
yeah and it's a rainy day as well. We
had such a beautiful days and now we
have a crap day. All this bit here
is all flooded.
Look at how it looks like that. It's
it's scary and a person needs to be
really careful especially these old
buildings. Everything can just start
falling apart. It's really really really
dangerous.
That is the the lifts.
Wow. Look at that. Oh my god.
[__] hell.
It's doing
The [__] was that?
Yeah, someone is
passing over there. Look at this. Nice.
>> Is it just someone came on?
Well, we need to be careful. This is
just like
loads of glass everywhere
and person needs to be careful.
Definitely.
Oh, there's another graffiti here.
From what I actually heard
is that it's big plans for the site and
the developer called the ambass
ambassador uh group I believe is turning
into a mixeduse area with homes, a
hotel, office spaces, shops and as well
some some care homes because they have
plenty space to be honest. Here is a lot
of space that can be used but at the
entrance I have seen that um the site
was going to be demolished.
Anyway, only the the builders can
actually say if it's actually safe or
not, if they actually need to demolish
everything. But yeah, it can be used for
all that stuff that uh I read about. Um,
which is cool. So, let's let's go around
and uh explore a little bit more.
They definitely could do a lot in this
place. The problem with those places is
they are not fast enough. If they when
they actually abandon a place like these
that they will have some plans in the
future, uh they should actually start
those plans not longer after when they
close the building because this is
basically what happened. As I said, this
building was closed in 2022.
I have seen a video someone was posting
a video was about like 8 months 8 months
like a year ago. So 2024
and this was all still intact because I
could see someone walking in and this
place all these windows they were still
intact because I remember to see that
statue over there. Well that sculpture
that is on the wall. Um, so if they
could have actually
been quicker enough, a lot of thing they
could be a lot of things they could
actually be still saved.
[laughter]
[gasps]
>> I like to do that kind of things. I like
to do that kind of things. You guys know
me. You guys know me from the previous
videos. I'm all the time pranking one
way or another.
>> It's the amount of metal sticking out.
>> Yeah, it's plenty of metal. Yeah.
The air cone.
Just look inside. There's still toilet.
>> Yeah, it's still toilet.
[__]
cuz it's like a lot of toilets.
Probably small offices maybe.
That house over there
>> is abandoned.
>> Is abandoned as well.
>> Yeah, but this is must must be part of
the same company.
>> Might be. We can always go there because
we is a way to go.
>> Yeah.
>> Over there. We'll see.
So that is basically the generators I
would say.
a lot
and all the power
is completely cut off.
Chilled water
lw
[snorts]
[laughter]
paparazzi.
>> Let's see what is on the other side.
Is this the kitchen or something?
>> What the [__] is this place here?
[laughter]
>> [__] Don't know. That is glue.
>> We should have masks, man. I'm not
kidding.
So here was the kitchen of the building.
Huge kitchen.
>> So probably the catering um lift is
somewhere. Ah might be there. Oh look
look look there. There is the catering
lift.
>> Wow.
>> You see cuz this is like a lot of like
water. Wait a second.
Yeah, it's definitely the cat ring. And
there was the canteen. There is the
canton.
That's like
uh
Well, let's go. Let's go. Let's go have
a meal.
Careful. Here is what is water. It's
fine.
Like all the air con.
There is like plenty of food and you can
serve yourself and the company pays.
[laughter]
Serve yourself in the company pace.
I'm now outside the Craig Ford house
that is very close. Well, it's basically
the one that we could see from the
credential building just over there.
That is the predential building. This is
the house that stays behind. Uh it was
some guys that they were walking walking
around and they said this is the Craig
Ford house. uh is not connected with the
credential uh building, but somehow they
recommended for us to if we want to go
inside to actually take some masks
because it's really moldy and it can
damage the the lungs to be honest
because even I I just got in uh just for
for a few seconds and I could smell it
and like how moldy is inside the
humidity. So yeah, it can be a risk. So,
it's not it's not worth it. Uh they said
it's good to to actually have it with
with the masks. Um uh so we will
definitely come back.
>> Yeah. And the boards as well. So that is
like because the guys they are just
upstairs. They are just up there.
And looks cool. Looks cool.
Uh but the thing is definitely better to
to get the masks to go inside. So yeah.
[music]
Yeah. A lot here. Yes. They start doing
some demolition.
>> Definitely.
>> Not been here.
>> Yeah, we have not been actually here.
But here is definitely they start doing
some demolition. This is not someone
that comes here to do some like
vandalism. This was definitely someone
they start actually destroying just
Yeah.
But now it gets the the question mark.
Are they going to demolish all the
building or are they going to refurb all
the building? They will restore all the
building. I would like to see.
>> I think I'm going to need a piece of
brick. I need it in the house.
[laughter]
>> Yeah, cuz I'm doing something. I need to
hold it in the
>> cut. I kind of had to cut it because he
was like saying that he's going to take
a brick and we need to cut this part
here because this is taking pieces of
the property which is abandoned somehow.
But anyway, it shouldn't happen.
Shouldn't happen.
[clears throat] It shouldn't happen.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
It's windy. It's actually really windy.
Honestly, I think that we actually have
seen everything what we could see
besides the the damage all over the the
building which is a shame.
Um
it's just walls, glass, pieces of
furniture, carpets,
lamps,
>> a lot of
>> cables, wires, everything.
That is basically what is in the
building. uh that were once was used
because this here was the the main
entrance because you can see that here
it was the desk and is where is the the
sculpture. So here is the reception area
that is that sculpture that I was
showing. So definitely here was the main
entrance of the building. So, I hope you
guys enjoy um and uh looking forward for
the next exploring location. We can't
wait to find something else. To be
honest, we still need to have a look on
the on that on that house next to this
building, which it might be interesting,
but we definitely need to have the
masks. Um so, yeah, we are not going to
take the risk today because we don't
want to get healed. Even sometimes
people like to [snorts]
uh to risk it but these kind of things
they are not worth it because you you
might not feel it when you go home. You
might start feeling in a few days is
when you start feeling like or you're
you're breathing or something you might
start coughing and you start wondering
why actually that happened. Well,
the reason why is if you breed that kind
of Oh,
[laughter]
it's my friend that is bringing a
souvenir. A souvenir. So, yeah, guys.
Much love and I will see you all in the
next one. Peace out.
Peace out, guys.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Someone close the door. Okay.